<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>‘ajam session</title>
    <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ‘ajam session</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/kwd-manchester.png</url>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/kwd-manchester.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blah blah</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/posts/thingy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/posts/thingy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are still in the planning stages of this workshop.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/</guid>
      <description>‘ajam session is an upcoming workshop (still in the planning stages; we are looking for a few more participants) on the theme of premodern literary exchange between Persian and Arabic, to be held at the Freie Universität Berlin on 27&amp;ndash;28 October 2022. This is intended to be an uncommon gathering&amp;mdash;perhaps the first of its kind in recent memory&amp;mdash;for scholars who work with textual sources in both Arabic and Persian, and whose research addresses the long interplay between the two literary traditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop participants</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/participants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/participants/</guid>
      <description>Participants are listed alphabetically by surname (except that the host is last). The Dr. title is used where applicable, but other titles are omitted. Please direct any questions or inquiries to Theodore Beers.
Dr. Vahid Behmardi Associate Professor of Arabic and Persian Literature, Lebanese American University
Dr. Behmardi will be presenting remotely.
Dr. Philip Bockholt Assistant Professor, Westfälische Wilhelms-Universität Münster
Dr. Yoones Dehghani Farsani Department Member, Orientabteilung, Staatsbibliothek zu Berlin &amp;ndash; Preußischer Kulturbesitz (Academia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop program</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/program/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop venues</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/venues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/venues/</guid>
      <description>Accommodation Participants who are coming from out of town will be staying at the Seminaris CampusHotel, just a few minutes’ walk from the building where our meetings will be held. The address of the hotel is Takustraße 39, 14195 Berlin.
Main workshop sessions All of our meetings on the FU campus will be held in the “Holzlaube” building, whose street address is Fabeckstraße 23&amp;ndash;25. There is a corner entrance at the intersection of Fabeckstraße and Arnimallee that should be convenient to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
