<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>‘ajam session</title>
    <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ‘ajam session</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/kwd-manchester.png</url>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/kwd-manchester.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>For guests: How to watch/participate remotely</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/posts/spectate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/posts/spectate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A link to an online meeting will be available upon request.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use this site</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/posts/how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/posts/how-to/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of the basic information that workshop participants and guests will need is
available here. You can navigate to different sections of the site using the
menu at the top of the page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/about/</guid>
      <description>‘ajam session is an upcoming workshop on the theme of premodern literary exchange between Persian and Arabic, to be held at the Freie Universität Berlin on 27&amp;ndash;28 October 2022. This is intended to be an uncommon gathering&amp;mdash;perhaps the first of its kind in recent memory&amp;mdash;for scholars who work with textual sources in both Arabic and Persian, and whose research addresses the long interplay between the two literary traditions.
Far too often, classical Persian and Arabic literature have been taught and studied at universities as though they can be siloed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop participants</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/participants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/participants/</guid>
      <description>Participants are listed alphabetically by surname. Please direct any questions or inquiries to Theodore Beers.
Presenters Dr. Theodore Beers Postdoctoral Research Fellow, ERC project AnonymClassic, Freie Universität Berlin (homepage)
Prof. Dr. Vahid Behmardi Associate Professor of Arabic and Persian Literature, Lebanese American University (profile)
Dr. Behmardi will be presenting remotely.
Prof. Dr. Philip Bockholt Assistant Professor of the History of the Turco-Persian World, Westfälische Wilhelms-Universität Münster (Academia.edu page)
Dr. Yoones Dehghani Farsani Department Member, Orientabteilung, Staatsbibliothek zu Berlin &amp;ndash; Preußischer Kulturbesitz (Academia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop program</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/program/</guid>
      <description>Day 0: Wednesday, Oct. 26 Details to be filled in shortly&amp;hellip;
StaBi visit and manuscript viewing, 14:30&amp;ndash;17:00, Potsdamer Straße 33, 10785 Berlin Informal welcome dinner for those already in town, time TBD, probably at Piaggio, Königin-Luise-Straße 44, 14195 Berlin Day 1: Thursday, Oct. 27 Certain details still being finalized&amp;hellip;
Morning reading session (for those interested), 10:00&amp;ndash;11:30, in the downstairs room (see venues); coffee at least will be available Opening remarks by Beatrice Gründler and Theodore Beers, 12:00&amp;ndash;12:30 Afternoon presentations (total 45 minutes each; ~20 minutes for the presentation itself), 12:30&amp;ndash;17:30 James White, &amp;ldquo;Medieval Persian Court Poets as Readers of the Arabic Corpus: Bilingual Approaches to the Ghaznavid Nasīb&amp;rdquo; Jaakko Hämeen-Anttila, &amp;ldquo;Jawidan Khirad and Its Translation into Arabic and Persian&amp;rdquo; Philip Bockholt, &amp;ldquo;Introducing a New Research Project on Knowledge Transfer and Translation among Arabic, Persian, and Turkish in the Ottoman World&amp;rdquo; Tobias Sick, &amp;ldquo;On the Ottoman Reception and Adaption of the Pandnāma-yi &amp;lsquo;Aṭṭār: Translation as Process and Product in the Early Modern Ottoman Empire&amp;rdquo; Pegah Shahbaz, &amp;ldquo;A Medieval Literary Jigsaw: The Persian Corpus as a Reservoir for Arabic Literature&amp;rdquo; A short catered lunch will be served at the workshop venue after the first paper (to avoid having it occur too late), around 13:15 There will also be a coffee break (with snacks) between the third and fourth papers Spanish Embassy-sponsored event about Kalīla and Dimna (incl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop venues</title>
      <link>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/venues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.theobeers.com/ajam-session/venues/</guid>
      <description>Accommodation Participants who are coming from out of town will be staying at the Seminaris CampusHotel, just a few minutes&amp;rsquo; walk from the building in which our meetings will be held. The address of the hotel is Takustraße 39, 14195 Berlin.
Main workshop sessions All of our meetings on the FU campus will be held in the &amp;ldquo;Holzlaube&amp;rdquo; building, whose street address is Fabeckstraße 23&amp;ndash;25, 14195 Berlin. There is a corner entrance at the intersection of Fabeckstraße and Arnimallee that should be convenient to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
